From reading the introduction,
读了引言后
we see that the authors refer to
我们发现作者将投资者情绪
investor sentiment as the positive or negative views of investors,
称为投资者的正面或负面观点
especially individuals who tend to cluster their orders around a market open.
尤其针对喜欢在开盘前发出大量委托的个人
The authors also define overnight returns as the close to
作者还将隔夜收益率定义为
open returns and describe the following hypothesis.
收盘到开盘收益率并提出了以下假说
Individual investors may notice attention
个人投资者可能会注意到重大事件
getting events and may then choose to trade on those events.
然后选择根据这些事件交易
Since many of them have day jobs,
由于他们大部分白天都有工作
they may place trades aftermarket clothes that would be executed the following morning.
所以他们在收盘后发出交易 交易会在第二天早上执行
The hypothesis continues to assume that
假说继续认为
these overnight trades may be subject to mean-reversion by the middle of that second day.
这些隔夜交易可能会受到第二天中午均值回归的影响
Based on this, you may start thinking about how this can be useful as an alpha factor.
你可能会疑问 如何根据这些信息创建 alpha 因子？
Let's say, a stock's overnight returns are high.
假设股票的隔夜收益率很高
So, that morning, you see an increase in
第二天早上的开盘价
a stock's open price relative to the previous day's close.
比第一天晚上的收盘价高
According to this hypothesis,
根据假说
the stock is overbought and we may expect a correction in a form of a drop in the price.
股票被炒高 我们预计股价会下跌
So, if you calculate the overnight return of the stock,
如果你计算了股票的隔夜收益率
you can short the stock that same morning when the overnight return is high.
当隔夜收益率很高时 可以在早上做空该股票
However, that's not the effect that we will look to capture here.
但是 我们关心的并不是这种影响
There are ideas later in the paper that we will use to construct an alpha factor.
我们将根据论文后面的观点构建 alpha 因子
Also, in the introduction,
在引言部分
the authors state that they test for short-run persistence in overnight returns.
作者提到他们测试了隔夜收益率的短期持续性
This indicates some momentum in the overnight returns over a short term window.
表示隔夜收益率在短期内具有某种动量
If we continue reading in section two titled sample, variable definitions,
继续阅读第二部分
descriptive statistics, we can see that they're
标题为“Sample, Variable Definitions, Descriptive Statistics”
interested in a window of one week or five trading days.
可以看出 他们观察了一周或五个交易日的隔夜收益率
They calculate the average daily close to open return over
他们计算了一周的平均每日收盘到开盘收益率
a week as a measure of the persistence or momentum in sentiments.
从而衡量情绪的持续性或动量
Again, based on this information,
你可以根据该信息
you can think about how
思考如何在
this weekly average momentum factor might be used in a theoretical portfolio.
理论投资组合中利用这种每周平均动量因子
If according to the hypothesis,
根据假说
the weekly average close to open return for a stock is high and positive,
如果股票的每周平均收盘到开盘收益率是很高的正数
we might want to buy more shares of that stock with
我们可能会买入更多该股票
the assumption that the positive returns will continue in the short run.
认为正收益率在短期内会继续保持
Finally, the abstract also identifies a third possible factor.
最后 摘要还提出了第三种潜在因子
With the hypothesis that in the longer term,
假设指出
stocks with high overnight returns under perform.
长期看来 隔夜收益率高的股票将表现不佳
In other words, in a longer time window,
也就是说 在更长的时间窗口内
stocks exhibit mean reversion.
股票会出现均值回归
If we go to section five titled longer-term returns,
转到第五部分“Longer-term Returns”
the hypothesis based on
作者根据其他论文
other papers is that stocks that are more attractive to speculators
提出了一种假说：如果股票对投机者来说更有吸引力
and therefore see more near term
近期可能具有正收益率
positive returns may end up under performing over the next 12 months.
那么在接下来的 12 个月内可能会表现不佳
However, this also is not the effect we will look to capture here.
但是 这也不是我们要寻找的影响